



NG. THI THANH QUYNH

- **1** 05/01/1995
- **** 0933.848.828
- ₱ 192/16 Luy Ban Bich, Ward Hoa Thanh, District Tan Phu, Ho Chi Minh City.
- Female
- □ thanhquynh2512@gmail.com
- i www.facebook.com/thanhquynh512

OBJECTIVE

With a bachelor's degree and working experience in pharmacy, I want to work and develop myself at **SALE ADMIN** in a dynamic environment where I can devote my youth and enthusiasm to achieve challenging goals. Through that I can learn more and develop myself in high position.

EDUCATION

PHARMACY

Oct 2014 - Nov 2017

UNIVERSITY OF MEDICINE AND PHARMACY, HCM CITY (YDS)

Graduated with Good

WORK EXPERIENCE

REGULATORY AFFAIRS - ASSISTANT

Mar 2018 - Sep 2019

Y-MED PHARMACEUTICAL LTD. CO.

- Contacting to manufacturer from India, UAE, Italy, ...and agency in VN to get dossiers, documents according to requirements for checking and submission to DAV
- Following up the registration process and result and report to MFR and manager
- Preparing and providing the legal and administrative documents for registration purpose
- Updating and informing to the manufacturers about new circulars, new regulations, ... relate to the drug registration in Vietnam
- Supporting other departments (Tender, Sale, Import,...) about the documents of products.

OC STAFF

Aug 2017 - Feb 2018

BOSTON PHARMA CO.,

- Having knowledgement about GLP, GMP
- Using equipments in Lab: HPLC, UV,.. to test quality of drug
- Making report for testing result

SKILLS

Organization

INTERESTS

Listening to music

Singing

Travelling, Exploring

Reading book

High sense of responsibility

Creative and friendly, Team work

Computer skills (Word, Excel,...)

English (Wriring, Reading, ..